A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 31048], 1973-1978., Extent: 34 cu. ft. (34 boxes). (Box 1-34)
  - Subseries C. 1978
    - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupations correspondence (Box 33)
    - SCHEV- HEW- OCR proposed reporting forms (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Correspondence (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Correspondence (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Campus Committee (Box 33)
    - Off campus courses (Box 33)
    - Office space (Box 33)
    - Planning and budget (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Letters of intent (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Development of Personnel guidelines (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Misc. Advisory Committee (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Ad Hoc Personnel Committee (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Ad Hoc Personnel Committee (Box 33)
    - Advisory Council of Presidents (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Space Utilization Report (Box 33)
    - SCHEV, Tenure and Facility work load study (Box 33)
    - Signature Authorization (Box 33)
    - Significant issues (Box 33)
    - Site provisions (Box 33)
    - Slaughter report, Vocational and Technical Education (Box 33)
    - Special Training Staff, Itinerary (Box 33)
    - (Box 34)
    - Special Training, Correspondence (Box 34)
    - Special Training (Box 34)
    - Special Training (Box 34)
    - Solicitation of Contribution (Box 34)
    - Standards of Conduct (Box 34)
    - State Agency Auxiliary (Box 34)
    - State Employee Credit Union (Box 34)
    - State Fair (Box 34)
    - State-Federal Liaison (Box 34)
    - State Fire Marshall (Box 34)
    - State Police (Box 34)
    - Student Information System (Box 34)
    - Student Profiles (Box 34)
    - Student Services, Deans of (Box 34)
    - Systems Management Guide (Box 34)
    - Surveys and questionnaires (Box 34)
    - Transfer policies and credit evaluation (Box 34)
    - Tuition (Box 34)
    - Tuition and fees (Box 34)
    - Tuition Fees Study (Box 34)
    - VPI and SU (Box 34)
    - VCCCS-VCU Data Center Administrator (Box 34)
    - Va. Western CC (Box 34)
    - Hamel, Dr. Dana B., Federal Communication Commission (Box 34)
    - Virginia Municipal League (Box 34)
    - Virginia Plan for Higher Education (Box 34)
    - Germanna Community College Faculty Member Dismissal report (Box 34)
    - Faculty Appointment and Tenure Policy (Box 34)
- Series II: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 31216], 1974-1980., Extent: 30 cu. ft. (30 boxes). (Box 1-30)
  - AACJC annual meeting (Box 1)
  - AACJC miscellaneous (Box 1)
  - AACJC publication (Box 1)
  - AACJC publication (Box 1)
  - Academic programs (Box 1)
  - Accountancy, State Board of (Box 1)
  - Accreditation, National Invitational Conference on (Box 1)
  - Accreditation and Institutional eligibility staff (Box 1)
  - ADP Plan (Box 1)
  - ADP Policy Committee meeting (Box 1)
  - ADP (Box 1)
  - ADP (Box 1)
  - ADP Policy Committee (Box 1)
  - ADP Policy Committee meeting (Box 1)
  - ADP Policy Committee meeting (Box 1)
  - ADP (Box 1)
  - ADP Policy Board (Box 1)
  - ADP Resource Sharing Task Force (Box 1)
  - ADP Policy Committee meeting (Box 1)
  - ADP Policy Committee meeting (Box 1)
  - ADP Subcommittee Appendix M (Box 1)
  - Administration, Dean of (Box 1)
  - Administration and Finance (Box 1)
  - Administration and Finance (Box 1)
  - Administration and Finance (Box 1)
  - Administration, Secretary of (Box 1)
  - Administrative Building (Box 1)
  - Administrative Officers (Box 2)
  - Administrative Assistant's Office (Box 2)
  - Adult Education Program (Box 2)
  - ADP Policy Committee (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Finance Committee (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Steering Committee (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Ad Hoc Committee on Organization (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Meetings, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Meeting 3/27/1975 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Meeting 4/28/1975 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Committee correspondence (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Meeting 1/17/1975 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Meeting 6/19/1975 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Handouts (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Meeting 8/21/1975 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Meeting 10/20/1975 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, Meeting 12/18/1975 (Box 2)
  - Aerospace Education Foundation (Box 2)
  - Active programs, information given Mr. Cox (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action Plan 1975 (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action working papers, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action Plan 1978 (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action Plan of 1974 (Box 3)
  - Affirmative Action 1975 (Box 3)
  - Agricultural, Agribusiness Education (Box 3)
  - Air Force Educational Program (Box 3)
  - American Colleges Testing Program (Box 3)
  - American Colleges Testing Program (Box 3)
  - American Association for Higher Education, publication (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education (Box 3)
  - Annual meeting, Virginia Community College System (Box 3)
  - Annual reporting (Box 3)
  - Applications (Box 3)
  - Apiculture (Box 3)
  - Army Reserve - VCCCS Cooperative Educational Program (Box 3)
  - Articulation guidelines (Box 3)
  - Anne Arundel Community College (Box 3)
  - Assistant Attorney General (Box 3)
  - Application (Box 4)
  - Appointment contracts (Box 4)
  - Appropriation Act 1977 (Box 4)
  - Appropriation Act 1978 (Box 4)
  - Armistead Report (Box 4)
  - Articulation agreement HB 6 (Box 4)
  - Articulation guidelines (Box 4)
  - Association of Community College Faculty (Box 4)
  - Attorney General's Office (Box 4)
  - Attorney General's Office (Box 4)
  - Audit- Community College of Virginia Educational Foundation, Inc. (Box 4)
  - Audit of productivity (Box 4)
  - Audio visual (Box 4)
  - Audit of productivity committee (Box 4)
  - Bar Association - Virginia Paralegal programs (Box 4)
  - Bird Report (Box 4)
  - Bicentennial (Box 4)
  - Bicentennial (Box 4)
  - Biographical sketch Dana B. Hamel (Box 4)
  - Biographical sketches, forms (Box 4)
  - Bird, Senator Lloyd C. (Box 4)
  - Bliley, Mayor Thomas J. (Box 4)
  - Bluefield College (Box 4)
  - Board, Local (Box 4)
  - Board, Local (Box 4)
  - Board, Local, Relations (Box 4)
  - Board, Local, Members (Box 4)
  - Boards, Self study manual (Box 4)
  - Board of Visitors, All colleges (Box 4)
  - Bond issue referendum, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Bond issue, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Bond issue, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Bond issue, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Bond issue, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Bond issue, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Bond issue, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Bond issue projects (Box 5)
  - Bond issue construction (Box 5)
  - Brethren Evangelist (Box 5)
  - Brevard Community College (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1974-1976 (Box 5)
  - Budget contingencies, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Boushall, Thomas C. (Box 5)
  - Division of Budget, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Division of Budget, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Budget guidelines (Box 5)
  - Budget hearings, House Appropriations Committee (Box 5)
  - Budget, Long term plan (Box 5)
  - Budget, Department print outs (Box 5)
  - Budget office, Institutional Projections (Box 5)
  - Budget, M & O funding (Box 5)
  - Budget, M & O funding (Box 5)
  - Budget Office (Box 5)
  - Budget reversion (Box 5)
  - Budget responses from colleges (Box 5)
  - Budget and staffing guidelines (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1980-1982 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1976-1978 (Box 5)
  - Budget (Box 5)
  - Brochures (Box 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Division of (Box 5)
  - Cable television (Box 6)
  - Cagle, Vice Admiral Malcolm W. (Box 6)
  - Calendar of events (Box 6)
  - Calendars (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay Project (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay Quarterly Progress Reports (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay Priority (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay Process (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay Priorities (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay Priority Groups (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay (Box 6)
  - Case study (Box 6)
  - CETA contracts (Box 6)
  - Chamber of Commerce, US (Box 6)
  - Chamber of Commerce, US (Box 6)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Va., Education Committee (Box 6)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Va. (Box 6)
  - Challenge Examination Fees (Box 6)
  - Chancellors memos, Executive Assistant to the Chancellor (Box 6)
  - Chancellors memos to VCCS Presidents (Box 6)
  - Chancellors memos to Dr. Hamel, Personal (Box 6)
  - Chancellors memos to Dr. Hamel (Box 6)
  - Chancellors memos to Dr. Hamel (Box 6)
  - Chancellors Office (Box 7)
  - Chancellors Salary (Box 7)
  - Chancellors memos, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Memoranda to the Chancellors Directors Advisory Council, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
  - Chancellors Faculty Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Chancellors Faculty Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Chancellors Faculty Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Chancellors memos, Executive Assistant to the Chancellor, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Chancellors memos to State Board of Community Colleges, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Chancellors Advisory Council of Presidents, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Car (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, 1976, Budget and Finance (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, 1976, Executive Committee Members (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, 1976, Curriculum and Program Committee (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, 1976. Building and Site Committee (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's memos to State Board of Community Colleges, 1976, State Board Members (Box 7)
  - Chancellor memos to Deputy Chancellors, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Chancellors Memos, Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Chancellors Memos to VDCC Staff, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Change Magazine Board of Trustees Luncheon, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Coastal Plains Regional Commission (Box 7)
  - Community College Faculty (Box 7)
  - Community College Review Editorial Board Committee, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Community College Curriculum policy (Box 7)
  - Community Colleges, Enabling Act (Box 7)
  - Community College Policy, Presidential evaluation (Box 7)
  - Community College Review, Editorial Board Committee (Box 7)
  - Community College Policy, Demonstration (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, New degree programs (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Operating manual changes (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Personnel dismissal (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Tuition and residency requirements (Box 8)
  - Memos to VCCS Presidents, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Student activities and athletics (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Off campus programs (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Chart presentation (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Purchase of property (Box 8)
  - VCCS Cash receipts, 1974 (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Naming colleges (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Policy manual changes (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Off campus courses (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Occupational technical students (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Use of facilities (Box 8)
  - Community College Policy, Disciplinary action (Box 8)
  - COPA (Council on Post secondary Accreditation) meeting, 1977 August (Box 8)
  - COPA meeting, 1976 February (Box 8)
  - COPA meeting, 1976 January (Box 8)
  - COPA, Presidential accreditation search committee, 1974-1976 (Box 8)
  - COPA, Assessing nontraditional education summary report (Box 8)
  - COPA meeting, 1975 April (Box 8)
  - COPA meeting, 1978 October (Box 8)
  - COPA meeting, 1978 September (Box 8)
  - COPA meeting, 1975 January (Box 8)
  - COPA meeting, 1974 (Box 8)
  - COPA meeting, 1978 September (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1977 March (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1976 August (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1976 April (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1976 September (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1976 October (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1975 March (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1975 October (Box 9)
  - COPA meeting, 1975 September (Box 9)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act of 1973 (Box 10)
  - COPA, Dr. Dana B. Hamel (Box 10)
  - COPA, 1978 (Box 10)
  - COPA, 1978 (Box 10)
  - COPA meeting, 1978 February (Box 10)
  - COPA meeting, 1978 March (Box 10)
  - COPA meeting, 1978 April (Box 10)
  - COPA Nominations Committee (Box 10)
  - COPA meeting, 1978 May (Box 10)
  - COPA, 1977 (Box 10)
  - COPA, 1977 (Box 10)
  - COPA meeting, 1977 September (Box 10)
  - COPA meeting, 1977 August (Box 10)
  - COPA meeting, 1977 June (Box 10)
  - COPA meeting, 1977 May (Box 10)
  - C, Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - C, Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Conduct, Standard of (Box 11)
  - Course and program approvals (Box 11)
  - Condemnation proceedings (Box 11)
  - Conference calls (Box 11)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education, Central, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Construction programs, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - Consultant services (Box 11)
  - Continuing Education Plan, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Council on Criminal Justice, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence courses (Box 11)
  - Council of Presidents (Box 11)
  - Correspondence (Box 11)
  - Meetings (Box 11)
  - Council of Presidents for Public Colleges (Box 11)
  - Research and Information Committee of the Council of the Presidents (Box 11)
  - Council of the Presidents Information Effort, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Council of Post secondary Accreditation (Box 11)
  - Council of Visitors, 1977 (Box 11)
  - County Officials, Directory (Box 11)
  - County Officials, State of Virginia (Box 11)
  - Charles Cox, Richmond Times Dispatch articles (Box 11)
  - Charles Cox, Richmond Times Dispatch articles (Box 11)
  - Charles Cox, Richmond Times Dispatch articles (Box 11)
  - Charles Cox, Richmond Times Dispatch, Information given (Box 11)
  - Charles Cox, Richmond Times Dispatch, Information on programs requested from (Box 11)
  - Credit cards (Box 11)
  - Mr. Crooks (Box 11)
  - CUPA (College and University Personnel Association) (Box 11)
  - Curricula Approved for the Virginia Community College System (Box 11)
  - Curriculum, Six Year Master Plan (Box 11)
  - Curriculum, VCCCS (Box 11)
  - Day care facilities (Box 12)
  - Deaf, Virginia Council of (Box 12)
  - Developmental Disabilities Projects (Box 12)
  - Dissertation Community College (Box 12)
  - Economic Research and Development, Bureau of (Box 12)
  - Editorial, A Success Story (Box 12)
  - Editorial Board, Community Colleges (Box 12)
  - Education, House Bill 563 (Box 12)
  - Education, Commission of the States (Box 12)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Educational Improvement Program, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Education, Secretary of (Box 12)
  - Education Programs, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Education Programs, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Education, Secretary of Governor's Office, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Education, Secretary of Governor's Office, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Education, Secretary of Governor's Office, 1977 (Box 13)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1977 (Box 13)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1978 January - August (Box 13)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1978 September - December (Box 13)
  - Education, Secretary of, Senate Bill 315 (Box 13)
  - Educational Programs, Division of, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Education, Higher, Questions relating to responses from President, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Educational Programs monthly reports, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Educational Programs, Division of (Box 13)
  - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the needs of, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Election, State, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Electricity Costs Commission, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Employee selection procedure (Box 13)
  - Engineering and buildings, Division of, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Engineering and buildings, Division of, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Emory and Henry College (Box 13)
  - Employment Commission, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Engineers Joints Council, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Enrollments, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - Enrollments, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Enrollments (Box 14)
  - Enrollment projections (Box 14)
  - Enrollments, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Enrollment Definitions Committee (Box 14)
  - 2-B forms, 1974-1976 (Box 14)
  - Enrollment booklet, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Enrollments, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Enrollment booklet, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Enrollments, Off campus programs (Box 14)
  - Enrollments, L-1 Report, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Enrollments, L-1 Report, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 14)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1973-1976 (Box 14)
  - Equal Opportunity, The Virginia Plan (Box 14)
  - Equal Opportunity, The Virginia Plan (Box 14)
  - Equal Opportunity, Virginia Plan for, Executive Order #1, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Equal Opportunity, Virginia Plan for, Executive Order #1, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Faculty Evaluation (Box 14)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee (Box 14)
  - Faculty Committee, Ad Hoc (Box 15)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee to Chancellor (Box 15)
  - Faculty Senate of Virginia (Box 15)
  - Faculty Evaluation, Ad Hoc Committee (Box 15)
  - Faculty contract (Box 15)
  - Facilities, Planning and Engineering, 1974-1976 (Box 15)
  - Facts and Figures, Virginia, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Faculty sick leave (Box 15)
  - FBI (Box 15)
  - Federal funding (Box 15)
  - Federal Funds, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - Federal Programs, Office of (Box 15)
  - Federation of Regional, Las Vegas Accrediting Committee, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Ferrum College, 1974-1978 (Box 15)
  - Finance, Director of (Box 15)
  - Financial Aid Services (Box 15)
  - Financial Aid, Students (Box 15)
  - Financial reports, 1974-1976 (Box 15)
  - Financial reports, 1972-1974 (Box 15)
  - Florida State University (Box 15)
  - F, Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Forum Club (Box 15)
  - FRACHE (Federation of Regional Accrediting Commissions of Higher Education), Correspondence (Box 15)
  - FRACHE-NCA meeting, 1974 February (Box 15)
  - FRACHE-NCA Liaison Committee meeting, 1974 March (Box 15)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 15)
  - G, Miscellaneous (Box 16)
  - Galbreaith, Don, Correspondence (Box 16)
  - Galbreaith, Don, Itinerary and correspondence (Box 16)
  - Garrett, Stacy, Assistant Attorney General (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, Members and Committees, 1975 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1974 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, House of Delegates, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, Senate, 1975 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1973 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1974 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1974, Carry over items (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1975 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1973 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1975 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1977 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1976 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1976 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1976 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly on Higher Education (Box 16)
  - General Assembly, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
  - General Assembly, SJR 96, 1977 (Box 17)
  - General Electric Co. (Box 17)
  - General Services, Dept. of (Box 17)
  - George Mason University (Box 17)
  - George Mason University (Box 17)
  - George Washington University (Box 17)
  - Governor's Manpower Planning Council, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Governor's Manpower Planning Council, Meeting Materials (Box 17)
  - Governor's Manpower Services Council (Box 17)
  - Governor's Manpower Planning Council, 1974-1975 (Box 17)
  - Governor's Manpower Services Council (Box 17)
  - Governor's Manpower Services Council (Box 17)
  - Governor's Office, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Authorizations (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Executive Assistant (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Miles Godwin, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Miles Godwin, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Miles Godwin, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Manpower Services Council (Box 18)
  - Governor's Manpower Services Council (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Memos to Agency Heads (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Policy Memorandum (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Secretaries (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Secretary of Administration, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, Secretary of Transportation, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Office, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Governor's Manpower Services Council (Box 19)
  - Grades and Grading, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Graduation Awards Conferred, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Graduates, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Grades and Grading, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Graphics Coordinator (Box 19)
  - Gray, Senator Elmon T., Meeting (Box 19)
  - Grievance by Educational Programs, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Grievance procedure for classified employees (Box 19)
  - Grievance policy (Box 19)
  - Guidelines for Academic Preparation of Faculty (Box 19)
  - H, Miscellaneous (Box 19)
  - Hamel, Dr., Speeches, 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Handbook, Employees (Box 19)
  - Harris, Norman (Box 19)
  - Harvard University (Box 19)
  - Helms, Jessie (Box 19)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Dept. of., 1975 (Box 19)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Dept. of., 1973-1976 (Box 19)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Dept. of., 1974 (Box 19)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Dept. of., 1975 (Box 19)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Dept. of., 1975 (Box 19)
  - Higher Education, Applications (Box 19)
  - Higher Education, Daily, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Higher Education, Study Commission, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Higher Education, Virginia Plan (Box 19)
  - Highways, Dept. of, 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - Highway Safety, 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - History of VCCS (Box 19)
  - Hollins College, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Honts, Bruce, E., 1976 (Box 19)
  - Hopkins Commission report, Management of Virginia State Government (Box 19)
  - House Bill 1355, Capital Outlay, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Industrial Development, Division of, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Information Officer, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Information Officer, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Information Officer, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Information Requests, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Instructions, Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Insurance, Dept. of (Box 20)
  - Internships (Box 20)
  - Internships (Box 20)
  - Interstate Organization and Association Memberships (Box 20)
  - Investigation by State Board Management (Box 20)
  - Invitations, 1974-1975 (Box 20)
  - Invitations, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Iowa Area Schools, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Israeli Showcase, 1976 (Box 20)
  - J, Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Journalism workshops (Box 20)
  - Journal of Education, Virginia (Box 20)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Division of, 1975 (Box 20)
  - JLARC (Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission) (Box 20)
  - JLARC, Program Evaluation for VCCS, 1975 (Box 20)
  - JLARC, Response and notes on Program Evaluation for VCCS (Box 21)
  - Kings Dominion (Box 22)
  - L, Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Law, The College Digest (Box 22)
  - Legislative services, Division of (Box 22)
  - Lehigh County Community College (Box 22)
  - Library, State (Box 22)
  - Lieutenant Governor (Box 22)
  - Lynchburg College (Box 22)
  - M, Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Management Services (Box 22)
  - Management Information System, Presidents' Advisory Committee (Box 22)
  - Management of Virginia State Government (Box 22)
  - Manpower Development and Training Service (Box 22)
  - Marine Corps Development and Education Command (Box 22)
  - Marine Sciences (Box 22)
  - Mary Baldwin College (Box 22)
  - Management by Objectives (Box 22)
  - Management by Objectives (Box 22)
  - Management by Objectives (Box 22)
  - Mary Washington College (Box 23)
  - Media (Box 23)
  - Medical College of Virginia (Box 23)
  - Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
  - Mental Retardation Advisory Committee (Box 23)
  - Metric system (Box 23)
  - Management Information System, 1974 (Box 23)
  - Management Information System, 1975 (Box 23)